Hi, and welcome to Artificial Intelligence.
嗨 欢迎来到人工智能课程
I'm David Joyner.
我是 David Joyner
&gt;&gt; And I'm Arpan.
我是 Arpan
We're here to get you started on this exciting subject.
我们之所以在这 是为了带你开启这场激动人心的人工智能之旅
AI has been a cornerstone in my research,
人工智能一直是我研究的基石
from cognitive modelling to robotics challenges.
从认知模型到机器人学都离不开它
In my PhD, I focused on computer vision, and
在攻读博士学位时 我的研究方向是计算机视觉
how it is used by intelligent agents to accomplish visual tasks.
以及智能体使用计算机视觉来完成视觉任务的方式
&gt;&gt; On the other hand, my work in artificial intelligence has been more
和他相反 我在人工智能领域的工作则更多是把
about using AI as a means to an end.
人工智能作为实现目的的手段
I'm interested in creating scalable personalized educational experiences and
我对创造可扩展的、个性化的教育体验比较感兴趣
one great way to do that is to build AI agents that work as tutors.
而要创造这种体验 制作人工智能体是个很好的办法 让智能体做导师
They build a model of student ability and use it to inform the guidance and
令其创建一个学生能力模型 并用该模型
the feedback and that they give over time.
来不断给出指导和反馈意见
While Arpan is interested in studying AI itself, I'm interested in AI as a tool.
Arpan 感兴趣的是研究人工智能本身 而我则倾向于把人工智能当工具看待
&gt;&gt; In this nano degree program, you will learn to apply the core concepts and
在本纳米学位课程中 你将学习如何应用人工智能的核心概念
techniques used in artificial intelligence from problem solving
和技术 如用搜索解决问题、
using search, to logic, planning, and probability.
逻辑、规划、概率等等
&gt;&gt; Along the way, you'll be given challenging,
在此期间 每个领域你都会遇到很有挑战性
yet fun AI problems to solve in each domain.
但也很有趣的人工智能问题
Once you've demonstrated mastery of these fundamental topics, you'll be able
一旦你完全掌握了这些基础知识
to choose an area of concentration to study in further detail, and
你就可以挑一个领域来进一步深入学习了
use as the basis for your Capstone project.
并在这些基础上开展顶点项目
&gt;&gt; Yeah, the skills you will learn with us can help you build a career in
对的 这些和我们一起学到的技能能帮你开启人工智能领域
artificial intelligence or a related field such as machine learning or
或是相关领域的职业生涯 如机器学习、
data science.
数据科学
Numerous companies and
许多公司
research labs are trying to solve real world problems using intelligence.
和研究实验室都在尝试着用智能来解决现实问题
&gt;&gt; Yeah, AI is becoming more and more common in products and
对的 越来越多我们日常使用的产品和服务
services we use every day, just take a look around.
都涉及到了人工智能 你只需看一眼周围便能发现
&gt;From self-driving cars, to intelligent thermostats,
从自动驾驶汽车、智能温控器
to autonomous robots, artificial intelligence is everywhere.
到自主机器人 人工智能随处可见